Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
8060
Kugelberg, Johan,
25 cubic feet 3,000 items.
Audio recordings, photographs, printed materials, publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection of approximately 3,000 rare and unique items documenting English and American punk and post-punk music, circa 1974-1986.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection of approximately 3,000 rare and unique items documenting English and American punk and post-punk music, circa 1974-1986. The collection includes original manuscripts, approximately 365 fliers and posters, approximately 1,300 fanzines, sound recordings, clothing, photographs, original art, and other ephemera. 157 books in the collection are cataloged separately.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kugelberg, Johan,
Subjects:
Punk rock music -- United States.; Punk rock music -- England.
Form and Genre Terms:
Fliers (printed matter).; Posters.; Fanzines.; Clothing.; Sound recordings.; Works of art.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Magazines and Fanzines
Box 1
Series II. Fliers and Posters
Boxes 2, 3-8
Series III. Newspapers
Series IV. Ephemera
Series V. Manuscripts
Series VI. Artwork
Series VII. Photographs
Series VIII. Audio
Series IX. Clothing
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Magazines and Fanzines
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, 24)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Issues 666-A (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Issues B-C (Box 25, Folder 34A)
  - Miscellaneous Issues D-H (Box 25, Folder 34B)
  - Miscellaneous Issues I, M (Box 25, Folder 34C)
  - Miscellaneous Issues N-O (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Issues P-R (Box 25, Folder 35A)
  - Miscellaneous Issues R-S (Box 25, Folder 35B)
  - Miscellaneous Issues S-T (Box 25, Folder 35C)
  - Miscellaneous Issues U-W (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - / *The Fanzine for the Blank Generation, March-July, 1977; Issue #: 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Publication location: Tustin, CA, United States
    Editors: Sue Starstruck, Alex Jones (Alex Rude)
  - 19, 1976-10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Publication location: London, Great Britain
    Editors: Margaret Koumi
  - 200 lb. Underground, 1997, July 1998; Issue #: 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Publication location: New Brunswick, NJ, United States
    Editors: Tony Rettman
  - 48 Thrills, 1977-03; Issue #: 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Publication location: Stevenage, Hertsfordshire, Great Britain
  - 48 Thrills, 1977; Issue #: 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Publication location: [Stevenage, Hertsfordshire?], Great Britain
    Notes: Corner stapled
  - 78 Quarterly, 1989-1992; Issue #: 1 & 2, 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Key West, Florida, United States
    Editors: Pete Whelan
    Notes: "Silver anniversary reissue"--Originally published 1967
  - 78 Quarterly, 1992-1993; Issue #: 7-8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 78 Quarterly, 1994-2000; Issue #: 9-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 99th Floor, 1983?; Issue #: 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Publication location: North Bergen, NJ, United States
    Editors: Ron Rimsite
  - Ache, 2000; Issue #: 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Publication location: Toronto, Canada
    Editors: Armen Svadjiam, Justin Wright
    Notes: Includes a torn-out page from an unidentified issue of Yourflesh
  - Adventures in Bereznik, 1994?; Issue #: 4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Editors: Simon Murphy
  - After Dark, June, 1969; March-August, 1973; Volume #: 5, 6, 11, Issue #: 2-4, 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Publication location: New York, United States
    Editors: William Como
  - After Dark, September-December, 1973; Volume #: 6, Issue #: 5,7, 8 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - After Dark, January-February, 1974; Volume #: 6, Issue #: 9, 10 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - After Dark, 1977-10; Volume #: 10, Issue #: 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alien Brains from the celebration of i-deth, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Publication location: [?], Scotland, Great Britain
    Editors: Nigel Jacklin
    Notes: Title taken from internal manuscript. "Alien Brains" was the name of Jacklin's band. The cover text on this publication is "…they make a overloaded dope dealer suckers in benches of religion"
  - All the drugs you can eat, 1983; Issue #: 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Publication location: Kinnelon, N.J., United States
    Editors: J. Crawford
    Notes: Entire fanzine is a diatribe about Maximum Rocknroll
  - Alternative Sounds, 1979-1980; Issue #: 6, 8, 17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Publication location: Coventry, Great Britain
    Editors: Martin
  - Alternative Ulster, 1978; Issue #: 8, 72 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Publication location: Bangor, Northern Ireland, Great Britain
    Editors: Roger, Gav, Junior, Alistair Graham, Dave Millar
  - Anarchy in the UK, 1976; Issue #: [1] (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - And/or notes, June, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Publication location: Seattle, United States
    Editors: Laura Brenner, Claudia Clement, Rene Fabre … et al.
    Notes: Final issue. Official publication of a Seattle art space.
  - Anfibi, 1983-05; Issue #: 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Publication location: Casalbruciato (Rome?), Italy
    Notes: Saddle stapled
  - Angry, 1984; Issue #: 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Publication location: Edinburgh, Scotland, Great Britain
  - Announcing attitudes, Issue #: 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Editors: Charles Wyndham
  - Attack on Bzag!/Molotov Comics, 1984?; Issue #: 9 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Publication location: Manchester, Great Britain
    Editors: James Brown, Steve Wells
    Notes: Split issue of two fanzines
  - Audion, 1994-Spring; Issue #: 28 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Publication location: Leicester, Great Britain
    Editors: Steve Freeman, Alan Freeman
    Notes: Experimental/Avant Garde music fanzine
  - Audion Guide to Nurse With Wound, 1994; Issue #: [28a] (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: Supplement to Audion #28, which contained a long interview with Steve Stapleton of experimental music group Nurse With Wound. Primarily a discography.
  - Auguste Pages, The, 1980; Issue #: 13 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Publication location: Medford, MA, United States
    Editors: Count Joseph Viglione
    Notes: With "Count Viglione's Love and Flame Newsletter" #3, Jun 7, 1980. Possibly related to Varulven (below).
  - Aware, 1973; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Publication location: Brooklyn, NY, United States
    Editors: Steve Kolanjian
  - B Side, 1985, 1987?; Issue #: 10, 14, 22 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Publication location: New South Wales [Sydney?], Australia, Australia
    Editors: Simon Lonergan, Caroline Birkett
  - Back Door Man, April, June, December, 1975; Issue #: 2-3, 5 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Torrance, CA, United States
    Editors: Fred Patterson
  - Back Door Man, 1976-1978; Issue #: 6-15 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Editors: Fred Patterson, D.D. Faye
  - Back Issue, 1979-1980?; Issue #: 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Editors: Aidan Brennan, D. Fischer
  - Bam Balam, 1978-1979; Issue #: 8-10 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Publication location: Dunbar, East Lothian, Scotland, Great Britain
    Editors: Brian Hogg
    Notes: Inc. many discographies
  - Bananafish, 1988-199?; Issue #: 3?, 4, 5 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Publication location: Berkeley, CA, United States
    Editors: Seymour Glass
  - Bananafish, 199-; Issue #: 6-8? (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Publication location: San Francisco, United States
  - Bananafish, 1993?; Issue #: 9 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bananas, 1977; Issue #: 11 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Editors: Bob Stine
    Notes: Pop culture magazine published by Scholastic.
  - Bandits One to Five, 1996; Issue #: 4 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Editors: Jon [John Hunter?]
  - Beat It!, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Publication location: New York; Wilmington, DE, United States
    Editors: Julia Gorton, Rick Brown
    Notes: Includes letter from editor to Greg Shaw + flier
  - Bedloe's Island, 1972-Winter; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 3 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Publication location: Plainfield, VT (Goddard College), United States
    Editors: Jesse Farlowe
  - Ben Is Dead, 1994; Issue #: 24 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Publication location: Hollywood, CA, United States
    Editors: Darby, Carla Bozulich, Jessica Jones
  - Best, March, 1978; Issue #: 116 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Publication location: Paris, France
    Editors: Patrice Boutin
  - Beyond Our Control, July, September 1973; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Publication location: Bloomington, IN, United States
    Editors: Mr. Bear
    Notes: The phrase "due to circumstances," which appears alongside the title, does not seem to be considered part of the title by the editors.
  - Beyond Our Control, [1973]; Issue #: [Prospectus] (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Beyond the Blackout, 1984-1985; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Editors: Wendy
  - Biff! Bang! Pow!, 1978?; Issue #: 2 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Publication location: Sun Valley, CA, United States
    Editors: Lisa Fancher
  - Big Size Large, 1981? (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Publication location: Caithness, Scotland, Great Britain
    Editors: Gordon Hendry
  - Big Star, 1977-1978; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Publication location: Buffalo, NY, United States
    Editors: Bernard Kugel
  - Big Star Newsletter, April-August, 1977; Issue #: 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bikini Kill, 1991; Issue #: 2 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Publication location: Washington, D.C., United States
    Editors: Kathleen Hannah
    Notes: First publication of Hannah's "Riot Grrrl Manifesto"
  - Black Dwarf, 1982?; Issue #: 4 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Black to Comm, 1992, 1993, 1994; Issue #: 19-21 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Publication location: Sharon, PA, United States
    Editors: Chris Stigliano
    Notes: Also numbered vol. 2, no. 6
  - Black to Comm, 1997, 2000-2001; Issue #: 22-24 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Notes: Also numbered vol. 2, no. 9
  - Black to Comm, 2003-Late; Issue #: 25 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Blam!, ca. 1979-1981; Issue #: 1, 3 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Publication location: Chelmsford, Essex, Great Britain
    Editors: Peter Hall
  - Blast, 1984; Issue #: 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Editors: Jacqueline Sullivan, Niel Taylor
  - Blitz, July-August, 1982; Issue #: 43 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Publication location: Los Angeles, United States
    Editors: Mike McDowell
  - Bodycount, 1982? (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Seattle, WA, United States
    Editors: Don Howe, Sherry Shanabarger, Perry Phillips …
  - Bomp Newsletter, 1977; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Publication location: Burbank, CA, United States
    Editors: Greg Shaw
    Notes: Unbound (single sheet)
  - Bomp Newsletter, 1977; Issue #: 4-12, 14-22 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Bomp Newsletter, 1978; Issue #: 32-35 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Publication location: [Burbank, CA?], United States
  - Bomp Newsletter, Issue #: 1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Publication location:
  - Bop, 1982; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Publication location: Princeton, WI, United States
    Editors: Catherine Yronwode
    Notes: Published by Kitchen Sink Comics.
  - Bop Eye, 1981; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Publication location: Wirral, Merseyside, Great Britain
    Editors: Tim Gudgeon
  - Boring Fanzine, A, December 1977; Issue #: 3 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Glasgow, Scotland, Great Britain
    Editors: A. Moron
    Notes: Cover title: "An extra boring fanzine for Xmas and New Year."
  - Box, 197-; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Publication location: Visby, Sweden
    Editors: Mikael Lindebark
    Notes: With manuscript on verso of last page
  - Brain Lapse, June, 2009; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Publication location: Minneapolis, MN, United States
    Editors: Todd Mayberry
  - Bravo, September-October, 1976; Issue #: 41-42 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Publication location: München, Germany
    Editors: Gert Braun
  - Bravo, August, 1988; Issue #: 35 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Breakthrough, 1984; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 11A)
    Publication location: Gillette, NJ, United States
    Editors: Todd Abramson
  - Cabarte, 1981-06; Issue #: 7 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Publication location: Newtownabbey, N. Ireland, Great Britain
  - Caff, 1987; Issue #: 3 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Publication location: Malton, South Bretton, and South Croydon, Great Britain
    Editors: Bobby Teenstar, Pierre Entertainment
    Notes: Folder containing fanzine and flexidisc.
  - Cassette Gazzette, 1982?; Issue #: 7 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Publication location: Brussels, Belgium
    Editors: Alan Demeure
  - Cells, 1977; Issue #: 3 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Publication location: [London?], Great Britain
  - Chainsaw, 1977-1978; Issue #: 2-5 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Editors: Charlie Chainsaw
  - Chainsaw, 1981; Issue #: 11-12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cimarron Weekend, The, 1998-2000; Issue #: 5-7 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Publication location: Memphis, TN, United States
    Editors: Giles Palermo, Quentin Sabago
  - Circular, February 19, 1973; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 7 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: "A weekly news device from Warner/Reprise."
  - Circus, September 19, 1977; Issue #: 165 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Editors: Gerald Rothberg
  - City Fun, 1979-1980; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 10, 16, 17, 19 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - City Fun, 1980-1981; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1, 6, 18, 20, 25, 26, 19 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cle, 1977, 1978, 1980, 1981, 995; Issue #: 1, 3, 3A, 3B, 3X (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Publication location: Cleveland, OH, United States
    Editors: Jim Ellis
    Notes: With manuscript letter to Greg Shaw
  - Clima, 1982-03; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Publication location: Torino, Italy
    Editors: Giulio Tedeschi
    Notes: Cover includes possible alternate title: "Climateric Review"
  - Coalminer's Journal, 1982; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Publication location: Essex, Great Britain
    Editors: Duncan Jack
  - Coast, 1973-04; Volume #: 14, Issue #: 4 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Publication location: Beverly Hills, CA, United States
    Editors: Colman Andrews
  - Common Knowledge, 1979; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Comstock Lode, ca. 1977-1979; Issue #: 1-4 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Publication location: Twickenham, Middlesex, Great Britain
    Editors: John Platt, Mary Platt
  - Comstock Lode, ca. 1979-1982; Issue #: 6-10 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Confidential, 1977; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Publication location: Harpenden, Herts, Great Britain
    Editors: Pete Nic, Kally
  - Conflict, 1984; Issue #: 35, 36 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Wayland, MA, United States
    Editors: Gerard Cosloy
  - Conflict, 1986; Issue #: 39-42 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Flushing, NY, United States
  - Conflict, 1987-01/02; Issue #: 43-48 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Conflict, 1989-1991; Issue #: 49-52 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Contempo Culture, 1980; Issue #: 4 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Publication location: Austin, TX, United States
    Editors: Ellen Gibbs, Stewart Wise, Kathy Darr
  - Cool Runnings Reggae, 1981; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Publication location: Espoo, Finland
    Editors: Jah Frankie Jones
  - Crank, 1993-1994; Issue #: 4-5 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Publication location: Syracuse, NY, United States
    Editors: Marc Masters
  - Crash Bang Comic, ca. 1977-1979; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Publication location: Airdrie, Canada
    Notes: COVER ONLY.
  - Crawdaddy!, February, 1966-March, 1967; Issue #: 1-8 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Publication location: Swarthmore, PA, United States
    Editors: Paul Williams
    Notes: A later-printed facsimile
  - Crawdaddy!, May, 1967-April, 1968; Issue #: 9-13 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Crawdaddy!, 1968; Issue #: 14, 20 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Editors: Chester Anderson
  - Crawdaddy!, 1993-1995; Issue #: 1-8 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Publication location: Glen Ellen, CA, United States
  - Crawdaddy!, 1995-1997; Issue #: 10-18 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Publication location: Encinitas, CA, United States
  - Crawdaddy!, 2002; Issue #: 26 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Crazy, August, 1981; February, 1982; Issue #: 77, 83 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Editors: Larry Hama
  - Creem, July, 1971; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 3 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Publication location: Detroit, MI, United States
  - Creem, November, 1971; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 6 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Publication location: United States
  - Creem, December, 1971; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 7 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Creem, December, 1973; Volume #: 5, Issue #: 7 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Publication location: Birmingham, MI, United States
  - Creem, July, 1974; Volume #: 6, Issue #: 2 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cripes, 1977; Issue #: 7-8 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cross Now, [1980] (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cut, 1988; Issue #: 5 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Publication location: Norwich, CT, United States
    Editors: Steve Erickson
  - Dance Crazy, 1981? (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Editors: Tim Shmils
  - Daytrippin', 1999-Fall; Issue #: 8 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Publication location: Beltsville, MD, United States
    Editors: Trina Yannicos
  - De/Create, June, 1994; January, 1995; Issue #: 2, 4 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Publication location: Wellington, New Zealand
    Editors: Nick Cain
  - Death on the Rocks, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Déjà Vu, 1977; Issue #: 3 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Editors: Rob Kelly
    Notes: Includes signed typescript letter to Greg Shaw
  - Disaster, 1987-Summer; Issue #: 4 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Publication location: Pasadena, MD, United States
    Editors: Bill Callahan
  - Disco World, 1978-04; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 2 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Editors: Sharlene Zaso
  - DNA, January, 1985; Issue #: 39+40 (double issue) (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Publication location: Adelaide, Australia
    Notes: MAY be the home of the stray page with the Skrewdriver ad on the back- the Dose is from Perth
  - Essex New Wave, 1978; Issue #: 5 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    Editors: Henry
  - Exit, January, 1975; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 4 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Editors: Alan Powell
  - Eye, June, 1968; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Publication location: New York, NY, United States
    Editors: Susan Edmiston
  - Face, The, May, 1980; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Editors: Nick Logan
  - Fanatic, 1975; Issue #: 5 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Editors: Richard Adams, Heathcote Williams
  - Fandomania, June, 1986; Issue #: 1 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Publication location: Grangemouth, Stirlingshire, Scotland, Great Britain
  - Fanzeen, 1977-1978; Issue #: 1, 3 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Editors: Robert Barry Francos
  - Fanzine Fanzini, November, 1972; Issue #: One unnumbered issue (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Publication location: Canada?
    Editors: John Jacks, John Dowd
    Notes: Spiral bound
  - Feber, 1990-1991; Issue #: 2, 3 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Publication location: Malmö, Sweden
    Editors: Bo Sandell, Lennart Persson
  - Fifth Estate, 2005-Spring/Summer (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Publication location: Ferndale, MI/Liberty, TN, United States
  - File, 1977-Fall; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Publication location: Toronto, ON, Canada
    Editors: AA Bronson, Felix Partz, Jorge Zontal
  - Final Solution, 1980; Issue #: 6 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Publication location: New Orleans, LA, United States
  - Fishwrap, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Editors: Marty Wombacher
    Notes: Special issue on Brian Wilson's "Smile"
  - Flesh and Bones, 1983; Issue #: 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Middlesex, NJ, United States
    Editors: Jeffo
  - Flexipop, 1983; Issue #: 25 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Editors: Barry Cain, Tim Lott
    Notes: Includes 2 flexidiscs and poster
  - Flicks, 1977; Issue #: 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Editors: John Herlihy, Glenn Marks
  - Flip Side, 1977-1979; Issue #: 1, 4-15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Whittier, CA, United States
  - Flip Side, 1979-1980; Issue #: 16-18, 20-22 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Flip Side, 1981; Issue #: 26-27 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: "Greatest Hits vol. 1"-- a compilation of interviews from the first 16 issues.
  - Flip Side, December 1981-12; Issue #: 29, 30, 32, 34 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Flip Side, 1982; Issue #: 36, 38, 54 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Flow Motion, 1980?; Issue #: 1,3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Publication location: Leeds, Great Britain
    Editors: Ian Dobson, Gordon Alien
  - For the Loyal Followers of Meatmen, 1982? (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Publication location: Lansing, MI?, United States
    Notes: Possibly issued by Touch & Go.
  - Forced Exposure, 1981-1983; Issue #: 1-6 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Publication location: Watertown, Mass., United States
    Editors: Jimmy Johnson
  - Forced Exposure, 1986-1988; Issue #: 9-10, 12-13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Publication location: Newtonville, Mass., United States
  - Forced Exposure, 1988-1990; Issue #: 14-16 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Publication location: Waltham, Mass., United States
  - Forced Exposure, 1991-1993; Issue #: 17-18 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Found Magazine, ca. 2001; Volume #: 2, Issue #: (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Publication location: Canada
  - Fox, 1971?-Summer/Fall; Issue #: 6 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Publication location: Amsterdam, Netherlands
    Editors: Ricardo Vesga
  - Frieze, 2003-10; Issue #: 78 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Editors: James Roberts
    Notes: Perfect bound
  - Fruits, 2003; Issue #: 68 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Publication location: Fruits, [Tokyo]
    Notes: Japanese street style magazine.
  - Fumes, 1979-12; Issue #: 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Editors: John Gilhooly
    Notes: Side stapled
  - Future, 1977, 1978; Issue #: 1, 2, 4 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Publication location: Rochester, NY, United States
    Editors: Greg Prevost
  - Future Direction, 1978-1979; Issue #: 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Publication location: Pasadena, CA, United States
    Editors: Chere, Janaee
  - Fxxk Pxxk, April, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Editors: Mary Pic
  - Gabba Gabba Hey, 1977; Issue #: 3 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Publication location: Middlesbrough, Great Britain
    Editors: Alan Cornforth, John Hodgson, Mick Hylton
  - Geek, 1979-1980; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Editors: Paul Jamrozy, Nobby Nils
  - Generation X, 1977-1978; Issue #: 1-4 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Publication location: North Hollywood, CA, United States
    Editors: Jade Zebest, Zandra
  - Ghast Up, April, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Publication location: Stockport, Cheshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Martin; Mick Middles
  - Gleet, October, 1999; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Publication location: Victoria, Australia
    Editors: Matthew Pelaggi
  - Gneurosis, 1990; Issue #: 0 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Editors: Frater Patamath, Paul Condon, Soror Fractell(e)
  - Go, 1974; Issue #: 7 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Publication location: Sundyberg, Sweden
    Editors: Ingegerd Gustafsson
  - Gorilla Beat, 1980; Issue #: 5 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Publication location: West Germany, West Germany
    Editors: Hans-Jurgen Klitsch, Alfred Hebing
  - Granite City, 1979?; Issue #: 7 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Publication location: Aberdeen, Scotland, Great Britain
    Editors: Morag McCorkindale
  - Grinding Halt, 1981?; Issue #: 12 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Publication location: Reading, Great Britain
    Editors: Captain Callows
  - Gulcher, Issue #: related ephemera (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Notes: 3 pieces of ephemera relating to Gulcher, primarily dealing with advertising rates and publicity.
  - Gun Rubber, 1977; Issue #: 6 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Publication location: Sheffield, Great Britain
    Notes: Includes a pre-Smiths piece on Morrissey (as a New York Dolls fan).
  - Guttersnipe, 1979; Issue #: 4 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Publication location: Telford, Great Britain
  - Halana, 1996-1997; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Publication location: Ardmore, PA, United States
    Editors: Chris Rice
  - Happyland, 2001-2002; Issue #: 9-11 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Editors: Selwyn Harris